# **Curriculum Vitae**

### Gusakov Giorgi

**Date of Birth:** 30.12.1991.

Yiv, Prospekt Svobody 1-a,

+38 (093) 27-34-894

gusakov.giorgi@gmail.com

facebook.com/giorgi.gusakov

https://twitter.com/GiorgiGusakov

in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/reop-ruй-гусаков-b7887273/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/reop-ruй-гусаков-b7887273/</a>

**S** giorgi.gusakov



#### **About**

I'm a Hello! I am Giorgi Gusakov. Android Developer, Software Engineer with 3 years of experience.

I have many hobbies: Traveling aroun the world, meeting new people, playing and watching football (I'm Red Devil!), reading and thinking about quantum physics, thinking about how to save mankind from vices, etc. For more information meet me somewhere on Earth.

# **Education**

From 2014 to 2016	The National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic
(SPECIALIST'S	Institute"
<b>ACADEMIC</b>	Specialty, "Information Management Systems and Technologies"
LEVEL)	Specialty "Information Management Systems and Technologies"
From 2010 to 2014	The National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic
(BACHELOR)	Institute"
	Specialty "Computer Sciences"

#### **Work Experience**

*May 2017-present:* Working as an Android developer and Software engineer in Mo-Apps company

2016-2017: Worked as an android developer in remote company

**DREAMBIM** 

From 2015: Working as an Android developer at freelancer.com.

# Skills

#### **Professional Skills**

88%	ANDROID SDK	75%
70%	APIS	85%
81%	MATERIAL DESIGN	66%
	70%	70% APIS

# **Additional Skills**

JAVASCRIPT	63%	JAVA EE	67%
РНР	70%	SQL	84%
BLOCKCHAIN	41%	LINUX	53%
STRESS RESISTANCE	99%	GOODNESS	98%

# **Participations**

Finalist of the DevChallenge12 competition

# Languages

